Hello hello friends I welcome you to the smartphone team
friends if you
have a MediAssist policy and the insured
person is driving then for that
you are going to fill the reimbursement claim form,
in the next video I am going to
tell you how you can fill it,
let's start the video without delay, to
download this form
you can visit the official
website of MediAss and you can
download this form on their official website
so here we can go to
MediAss reimbursement claim form to we sell
by the insurance policy number so this
is you will write your policy number and the name of the
primary installer has to be written here, the primary installer has to write his surname here,
then the middle name will be written here, the address
of the prime assister has to be written here, take the
address and write the city here,
keep the state here, write these here and
here you have to write the phone number here and here you have to
give the Gmail ID here if the
person who was hospitalized  If he has any
insurance history then that detail has to be filled here,
details of these short slice which is the installed
person, the
details of the one who has been hospitalized have to be filled here, at the
end add
first name and madeline or you have to write this, if this is
my gender then set male or female and
paste Tamil, then the
date of birth of the person who has been hospitalized has to be
written,
relation to time being shot,
what is his relationship with the person who has been hospitalized, you have to take this here,
whatever question you have about the patient,
click here or
fill the address here, city here,
state here, pin code here and if you have email ID then
write that here
and hospitalization so this is the
hospitalization detail, you have to fill the
name of the hospital in which he has been admitted, you have to write it here,
after this you will go down you
can find the room category occupied written here, you have to tick the form of the person who has been
hospitalized,
then you
can tick the hospitalization written here  The
reason for their hospitalization has to be
adjusted accordingly.
Below will be the date of admission. The
points and the date of the person who was hospitalized, the date of
his admission in the hospital, the time of
admission, the day of
his discharge from the hospital,
then the time of his
discharge, then you will see the
details of claim below. I would like to tell you one thing,
you can claim for pre-hospitalization and main
hospitalization together or
you can do it separately, it
depends on you, so let's move ahead,
then hospitalization claim,
like I am going to claim pre-hospitalization, extended
and main claim together in the express and
I will
claim for post-hospitalization later, so it depends on you whether
you want to do these and post-hospitalization together for free
or you
want to do milk cream and pure
after that, it depends on you, so
like I am going to do it and Menaka, so
my only
I have written about my hospitalization experience, then
I have written my explanation of hospitalization here, then where you can
show it, you can see the plain mode of submitting it,
so I would like to tell you one thing that this
form that you are filling is
called form, you will also have to
get it along with it, so that form is also
filled chapter wise by the hospital people, so
you have to submit it, so you have to click on it
and you have to submit the main bill of the hospital,
then you have to
submit the breakup bill of the hospital, you have to submit all the receipts etc. that you have received in the hospital, you have to
submit the discharge summary also, if you have any pharmacy
experience, then
you will also get these messages between the pharmacy, that is,
you have received these messages on the day of
hospitalization, then you have to click on it accordingly, so the
PM, you have to submit it,
then you have to submit the main bill of the hospital, you have to
submit the breakup bill also
Then you do not have to
submit the receipts of all the payments you made in the hospital,
then the discharge summary of the hospital
also has to be submitted and if you are
claiming pharmacy then
you also need pharmacy bills etc. along with
their prescription is also necessary, so
after this you will go down,
here it is written you can read details of will
and closed, so if I get this done from the hospital then
I have written my maintenance amount here, I have written the
expenses of the opposite hospitalization
here and I have written my pharmacy expenses
exactly
and I have written the total amount I am going to
claim here,
then the primary in short, the
primary installed, you have to
write your PAN number here, then Prime
Resort, you have to write your account number here
and that Prime Resort, you have to
write your bank name and branch here along with it
and this IFSC code has to be
written, the question is why one should initiate,
these declarations must be filled in  You have to
take it,
then you have to sign the other inch with your own hand
and this is not daily and
please write it here and along with this you must have
also got this form, this is a
form for guidance, that is, how to fold it,
you can read it also,
after this you also got this platform, the
uniform text is also filled by the hospital people,
you do not have to fill anything in it, it will be
filled by the hospital people only, you do not have to fill anything in it,
after this let me tell you
which documents are required during the games,
apart from this if any other document is
required then the insurance company
told you that we need these documents, so first of all the
discharge
summary ES, after this send the claim form text plus
party text, you have to fill it, text BK
hospital people will fill in these hospital bills,
hospital breakup bill, hospital bill payment
receipt, that is, receipts of whatever payments you have made,
investigation report with prescription, that is,
whatever tests you have got done, blood
test done or CT scan done,
X-ray done, ultrasound done, whatever
means whatever tests have been done during hospitalization
Their reports are
prescription for them, bill with
prescription ID proof of institute
person, hospitalized ID proof of
primary short person, cancelled cheque of
primary in short person and the
car of the policy you would have got, then
these documents are required during normal e-claim,
apart from this if any other document is
required then the insurance company will
tell you that we need these documents
and if you have any question
related to this video then please
go to the comment box below the video and ask your question,
I will try my best to reply to them,
so I hope friends, you would have liked the
information that I have given you in the current video, if you
liked the video then
definitely like and share this video
and if you have not yet subscribed
to this Smartphone channel then please
subscribe to the Smartphone channel and
also press the bell to get information about every upcoming
latest video, so that's all for the current
video,
thank you for watching.